// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A literary genre is also known as literary _________.",
    answer: "A. composition",
    options: [
      "A. composition",
      "B. academic text",
      "C. essay",
      "D. epic"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "It is a short story designed to allegorically teach some religious principles, moral/ lessons, or general truths.",
    answer: "B. parable",
    options: [
      "A. fable",
      "B. parable",
      "C. narrative poem",
      "D. anecd"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "It is a brief story illustrating a moral or revealing general truths about human nature.",
    answer: "A. parable",
    options: [
      "A. parable",
      "B. narrative poem",
      "C. fable",
      "D. anecdote"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "He is a well-acclaimed writer who wrote the parable entitled “The Story of the Pencil”.",
    answer: "D. Paulo Coelho",
    options: [
      "A. Paul Coelho",
      "B. Paula Coole",
      "C. Paulo Colle",
      "D. Paulo Coelho"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The story “The Ants and the Grasshopper” is an example of a/an __________.",
    answer: "B. fable",
    options: [
      "A. parable",
      "B. fable",
      "C. narrative poem",
      "D. anecdote"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Parables and fables are very interesting to read because you will learn _________ from them.",
    answer: "C. moral/lesson",
    options: [
      "A. topic",
      "B. review",
      "C. moral/lesson",
      "D. immoral"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In the parable “The Story of the Pencil”, the _____ is the nondescript object that gives a powerful message.",
    answer: "A. pencil",
    options: [
      "A. pencil",
      "B. paper",
      "C. wooden stick",
      "D. umbrella"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "It refers to any electronic application that uses both words and pictures in a combination of text, voice, picture, or video.",
    answer: "B. multimedia",
    options: [
      "A. media",
      "B. multimedia",
      "C. printer/scanner",
      "D. projector"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The use of multimedia enhances the teaching of lessons and aims to __________ learners who are engaged in Online Distance Learning.",
    answer: "C. further educate learners",
    options: [
      "A. further confuse learners",
      "B. further waste learners’ time",
      "C. further educate learners",
      "D. further entertain with computer"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Videos, animation, text, images, and audio are all multimedia ________.",
    answer: "A. formats",
    options: [
      "A. formats",
      "B. components",
      "C. uses",
      "D. presentations"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Blogs, vlogs, webinars, and other interactive contents are multimedia ____. ",
    answer: "A. components",
    options: [
      "A. components",
      "B. uses",
      "C. formats",
      "D. presentations"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The AVI (Audio Video Interleave) that is developed by Microsoft is commonly used in video, cameras, and TV __________, and it plays well on Windows computers.",
    answer: "C. hardware",
    options: [
      "A. programs",
      "B. software",
      "C. hardware",
      "D. viewing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "“You can also download a multimedia presentation or play it live.” It tells us about multimedia _________.",
    answer: "D. benefits",
    options: [
      "A. uses",
      "B. formats",
      "C. characteristics",
      "D. benefits"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "“Digital storytelling allows students to improve their knowledge and increases skills such as writing, researching, and reading.” It tells us about multimedia ______________.",
    answer: "A. benefits",
    options: [
      "A. benefits",
      "B. formats",
      "C. characteristics",
      "D. uses"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "To make creative multimedia output, we can import images, audio, and video clips; however, we have to _________________ to avoid plagiarism.",
    answer: "D. cite sources",
    options: [
      "A. leave the webpages",
      "B. screenshot the images",
      "C. ignore the links",
      "D. cite sources"
    ]
  },
];
